Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. New business records, 1924-2007 and undated, bulk 1980-1989 RL.00731
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company. New business records
1924-2007 and undated, bulk 1980-1989
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company
RL.00731
88.0 Linear Feet
Founded in 1864, the J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) is one of the largest and oldest enduring advertising companies in the United States. The J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) New Business Records span the years 1924-2006, with the bulk of materials spanning 1980-1989. The collection combines the records of the New Business Departments of JWT's major U.S. offices: New York, Chicago, Detroit, Atlanta, and San Francisco, and includes presentations, memoranda, case histories, market research, and profiles of companies, industries, market segments, products and product categories. Topics addressed include the youth market, financial services marketing, food and grocery marketing, feminine hygiene and other personal products, and product branding. The collection includes photographs, audiocassettes, videocassettes, DVDs. Over 300 companies are represented in the collection, including Alitalia, Baskin-Robbins, Bell Atlantic, Circuit City, Eastern Airlines, Eyelab, Frito-Lay, Goodyear, Häagen-Dazs, HBO, Hyatt Hotels, IBM, Johnson & Johnson, Kodak, Kraft, Miller Beer, Morgan Stanley, Nabisco, Nestlé, Prudential, Schering-Plough, and the U.S. Navy. Many of the companies represented in the collection subsequently became clients of JWT, so there is some correlation between this collection and the JWT Account Files collection. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising, & Marketing History.
Access Restrictions
Collection is restricted.
Materials are closed to non-JWT researchers for 15 years from date of creation. Materials containing sensitive information relating to employment or other personnel issues are closed to non-JWT researchers for 40 years from the date of termination of employment, or 25 years from the date of the death of the employee.
Original audiovisual materials are closed to researchers until Use Copies can be produced. Contact Research Services staff for more information.
In addition, the Collection may contain materials to which the Acknowledgement of Legal Responsibilities and Privacy Rights form applies. Patrons must sign this form before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The J. Walter Thompson Company. New Business Records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 1987, with additions throughout subsequent years.
Collection Overview
The J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) New Business Records span the years 1924-2007, with the bulk of materials spanning 1980-1989. The collection combines the records of the New Business Departments of JWT's major U.S. offices: New York, Chicago, Detroit, Atlanta, and San Francisco, and includes presentations, memoranda, case histories, market research, and profiles of companies, industries, market segments, products and product categories. Topics addressed include the youth market, financial sservices marketing, food and grocery marketing, feminine hygiene and other personal products, and product branding. The collection includes photographs, audiocassettes, videocassettes, DVDs. Over 300 companies are represented in the collection, including Alitalia, Baskin-Robbins, Bell Atlantic, Circuit City, Eastern Airlines, Eyelab, Frito-Lay, Goodyear, Häagen-Dazs, HBO, Hyatt Hotels, IBM, Johnson & Johnson, Kodak, Kraft, Miller Beer, Morgan Stanley, Nabisco, Nestlé, Prudential, Schering-Plough, and the U.S. Navy. Many of the companies represented in the collection subsequently became clients of JWT, so there is some correlation between this collection and the JWT Account Files collection.
Collection Arrangement
Collection is arranged into the following series: General Files; Company Files; Product Category Files; Chicago Office Additions; Oversize Materials; Audiovisual Materials; and Restricted Materials. The Restricted Materials series consists of materials not currently open to general researchers. Original folder titles have been maintained where practical.
Related Material
Related materials may be found in the following Hartman Center collections of the J. Walter Thompson Company Archives:
Account Files
Advertising Vertical File
Corporation Vertical File
Jack Peters Papers
Additional related materials may be found in the following Hartman Center collections:
Bates Worldwide, Inc. Records
Charles McKinney Papers
John O'Toole Papers
Warwick Baker O'Neill Records
Advertising agencies; Advertising agencies -- United States; Advertising agencies -- United States -- History; Marketing research; Audiocassettes; DVDs; Photographs; Videocassettes; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History; J. Walter Thompson Company; J. Walter Thompson Company. San Francisco Office; Morgan Stanley & Co; Miller Brewing Company; Kraft Foods Company; Johnson & Johnson; International Business Machines Corporation; Häagen-Dazs (Firm); Hyatt Hotels Corporation; Home Box Office (Firm); J. Walter Thompson Company. New York Office; J. Walter Thompson Company. Detroit Office; J. Walter Thompson Company. Chicago Office; J. Walter Thompson Company. Atlanta Office; Bell Atlantic Corporation; Circuit City Stores; Alitalia (Airline); Baskin-Robbins (Firm); Frito-Lay, Inc.; Goodyear Tire and Rubber Company; Eastern Air Lines, Inc.; Eastman Kodak Company; United States. Navy; Nestlé; Nabisco Brands, Inc.; Schering-Plough Corporation; Prudential Insurance Company of America
- General Files, 1924-2006 and undated, 15 boxes
  Scope and Contents note
  Includes aggregate information about JWT's client base by year, gains and losses of clients; various account and new business prospect reports; biographical sketches of executives working in new business activities; and the files of some executives engaged in new business activities, including Richard Brecker and Milton Moskowitz. Oversize and Restricted materials have been physically relocated to their respective series and noted in the their logical location by an entry in brackets. Arranged alphabetically by topic.
  - Account Gains and Losses, 1960-1988
    - General, 1974-1988, 9 folders (Box 1)
    - General, 1974-1988 (Box 1a)
    - Account reports, 1983-1987 Sept., 10 folders (Box 2)
    - Account reports (continued), 1987 Oct.-1988 May, 10 folders (Box 3)
    - Account reports (continued), 1988 May-July (Box 3a)
    - Account reports (continued), 1988 July-1991 June, 9 folders (Box 4)
    - Account reports (continued), 1991 July-1994 Mar., 9 folders (Box 5)
    - Account reports (continued), 1994 Apr.-Aug., 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Miscellaneous files, 1987 (Box 6)
    - Multinational versus local, 1988 (Box 6)
    - Worldwide, 1988-1990, 1-5 of 12 folders (Box 6)
    - Worldwide, 1988-1990 (continued), 6-12 of 12 folders (Box 7)
    - Year End Submissions--Canada/USA, 1984, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Year End Submissions--USA, 1984, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Awards file, 1986-1988 (Box 8)
  - Brecker (Richard) files, 1962-1964
    - Business development, 1962 Apr.-1964 Sep. (Box 8)
    - Corporate advertising, 1963 Nov. (Box 8)
    - Miscellaneous papers, undated (Box 8)
    - New business list (prospect-progress report) 1964 Feb. (Box 8)
    - Research, 1963 Oct. (Box 8)
    - Volume groups, 1963 May-1964 Mar. (Box 8)
  - [Chicago Office, JWT planning toolkit, 2006: moved to Restricted Materials] (Box 8)
  - Chicago Office, JWT presentation photos, circa 1993 (Box 8)
  - Client lists, 1980-1992
    - JWT-USA, 1980 July-1992 Jan., 6 folders (Box 8)
    - North American client list, 1985 July-1992 Sep., 5 folders (Box 8)
    - Red Book listing, 1985 (Box 8)
    - Uniform Account List, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Clients and assignments--USA, 1960-1990 (Box 9)
  - Employee biographies
    - Clinton (Pat), Client Service Supervisor (Box 9)
    - Cochrane (Tom), Senior Vice President, Director of Print Production and Broadcast Traffic (Box 9)
    - Dochterman (Ludwig), Vice President, Associate Creative Supervisor (Box 9)
    - Hassett (Kathy), Vice President, Network Negotiator Supervisor (Box 9)
    - Hoffnagle (Wilson), Vice President, Network Supervisor (Box 9)
    - Kamerer (John), Vice President and Art Director (Box 9)
    - Krimezis (Cynthia), Account Supervisor (Box 9)
    - Lane (William/Bill), Executive Vice President, Executive Creative Director for JWT New York (Box 9)
    - Metter (Bertram/Bert), Chairman of JWT-USA (Box 9)
    - Mitchell (Bob), Senior Vice President, Associate Creative Director (Box 9)
    - Moodie (Alexandra), Media Supervisor (Box 9)
    - Murphy (Melissa), Senior Vice President, Management Director (Box 9)
    - Owett (Bernard/Bernie), Senior Vice President, Creative Director, 1966, undated (Box 9)
    - Paton (Michele), Media Supervisor (Box 9)
    - Scott (Bob), Senior Vice President, Group Account Director (Box 9)
    - Swartzentruber (Emily), Senior Vice President, New York Media Director (Box 9)
    - Other employees, undated (Box 9)
  - Generic inquiry response, 1992 (Box 9)
  - House advertisement strategies, 1989 (Box 9)
  - [J. Walter Thompson Company: An Analysis, 1938: Moved to Oversize Materials], 3 folders (Box 9)
  - [J. Walter Thompson Portfolio Comprising of Facts and Figures, circa 1924: Moved to Oversize Materials] (Box 9)
  - JWT organizational overview, undated (Box 9)
  - JWT strategic plan, undated (Box 9)
  - JWT-USA Effie submissions, 1992, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - JWT-USA 5 year history--income statement, 1982-1986 (Box 9)
  - Main mailing list, 1988 (Box 9)
  - Memoranda, 1992 (Box 9)
  - Memoranda, 1994-1996 (Box 10)
  - Moskowitz (Milton) files, 1962-1970
    - Case histories, multiple clients, 1965 Mar.-1966 Feb. (Box 10)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1962 Sep.-1970 Apr. (Box 10)
    - Prospects--progress reports
      - Chicago Office, 1960 Apr.-1970 Apr. (Box 10a)
      - Detroit Office, 1964 Feb.-1965 Sep. (Box 10a)
      - European Offices, 1963 June-1966 Mar. (Box 10a)
      - Hollywood Office, 1965 Feb. (Box 10a)
      - Los Angeles Office, 1960 Feb.-1970 Apr. (Box 10a)
      - Miami Office, 1960 May-1965 May (Box 10a)
      - New York Office, 1959 July-1965 Oct., 2 folders (Box 10a)
      - San Francisco Office, 1960 Feb.-1970 June (Box 11)
      - Washington, D.C. Office, 1960 Sep.-1965 Oct. (Box 11)
  - Multiple clients, case histories, 1986-1988, 3 folders; 1 folder moved to Oversize Materials (Box 11)
  - New business press clippings, 1992-1994, 1-6 of 20 folders (Box 11)
  - New business press clippings, 1992-1994 (continued), 7-14 of 20 folders (Box 12)
  - New business press clippings, 1992-1994 (continued), 15-20 of 20 folders (Box 13)
  - Presentations, 1924-2000 and undated
    - 1987, A Lesson in Humility (Box 13)
    - Agency presentation, 1924 (Box 13)
    - [An Intimate Picture of the World's Largest Advertising Agency, 1935: Moved to Oversize Materials] (Box 13)
    - Approach to New Business for the JWT Company, 1975 (Box 13)
    - [Atlanta Office new business presentation, circa 1984: Moved to Oversize Materials] (Box 13)
    - Company of Adventurers (Sam Meek), undated (Box 13)
    - Finalist challenge, 1993 Oct. 26 (Box 14)
    - Getting the Best, European managers meeting, 1987 (Box 14)
    - International Advertising, 1935 (Box 14)
    - International Advertising: Facilities of JWT, 1944 Aug. 8 (Box 14)
    - Just What Do J. Walter's Yesterdays Mean to J. Walter's Tomorrows?, undated (Box 14)
    - JWT-USA Most Distinctive Effective Advertising, 1983-1987 (Box 14)
    - JWT worldwide general presentation, 1992- 1993, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Largest Clinic of Advertising in the World, 1942 (Box 14)
    - Making Advertising Pay During the Depression, circa 1932 (Box 14)
    - Medium is the Message, 1992 Oct. 26 (Box 14)
    - New business presentation, 1945 (Box 14)
    - So What...? 1994 (Box 14)
    - [Successful Examples of Mass Education by Clients of J. Walter Thompson Company, circa 1965: Moved to Oversize Materials] (Box 14)
    - [The Future--Do We Get It? 2000: Moved to Restricted Materials] (Box 14)
    - Total Branding (Mexico), 1996 (Box 15)
    - Who is J. Walter Thompson and What Can They Do for Me?, undated (Box 15)
    - [Who We Are, circa 2000: Moved to Restricted Materials] (Box 15)
  - Printouts for leave-behind book, circa 1993 (Box 15)
  - Prospect lists, 1985-1988, 3 folders (Box 15)
  - Publicity, 1965-1967 (Box 15)
  - Regional advertising group pamphlet, undated (Box 15)
  - [Retail New Business Conference, 2005: Moved to Restricted Materials], 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Summary report mailing, 1988 (Box 15)
  - Traveling reel file, 1986-1988, 2 folders (Box 15)
- Companies Files, 1946-2005 and undated, 72 boxes
  Includes presentations, printed materials, clippings, background research reports; strategy and position papers. Oversize and Restricted materials have been physically relocated to their respective series and noted in the their logical location by an entry in brackets. Original folder titles have been retained. Arranged alphabetically by company or product, thereunder by topic.
  - A&P (Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company)
    - General files, 1989-1990 (Box 16)
    - [JWT-USA--A&P Clean Copies, 1990 Jan. 9: Moved to Oversize Materials.] (Box 16)
    - Presentations, 1990 (Box 16)
    - Project Eclair, 1990 Jan. 24 (Box 16)
    - Team member biographies, 1990 (Box 16)
  - ACME
    - Choosing An Advertising Agency for ACME, circa 1986 (Box 16)
    - Positioning for Strength, undated (Box 16)
  - Aetna Health Plans
    - Advertising agency questionnaire, 1993 (Box 16)
  - Albany Blue Cross and Blue Shield Plans
    - JWT internal discussion to pursue account, 1957 Feb. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 16)
  - Alberto-Culver Company
    - JWT account records, 1959 Feb-1965-June (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 16)
  - Alitalia Airlines
    - General files, 1988-1989 (Box 16)
    - Clippings, 1987-1989 (Box 16)
    - Competitive advertisements, 1989 (Box 16)
    - Creative Department, 1989-1990 (Box 16)
    - Credentials presentation, 1989, 1 of 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Credentials presentation, 1989 (continued), 2 of 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Florida, 1989 (Box 17)
    - Market overview, circa 1990 (Box 17)
    - Miami project, 1990-1991 (Box 17)
    - Promotional literature, 1988-1989 (Box 17)
    - Summer timetable, 1990 (Box 17)
  - Alitame sweetener (Pfizer)
    - General files, 1988 (Box 17)
    - New Step presentation, 1988 (Box 17)
  - Allied Lyons
    - Company profile, 1988 (Box 17)
  - Alpha Beta
    - Public relations records, 1986 (Hill and Knowlton) (Box 17)
    - [JWT-USA--Alpha Beta presentation book, 1986: Moved to Oversize Materials], 6 folders (Box 17)
  - Aluminium Limited
    - General files, 1959 Jan.-1962 Mar. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 17)
  - American Bakeries Company
    - General files, 1959 July-1964 Jan. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 17)
  - American Bankers Association
    - General files, 1946 Apr.-1958 July (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 17)
  - American Egg Board
    - J. Walter Cooks presentation, 1983 (Box 17)
  - American Gas and Electric Company
    - General files, 1955 July-1961 Jan. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 17)
  - American Greetings
    - Growth presentation, 1986 (Box 17)
    - How Can Advertising Pay Off for American Greetings? 1986 (Box 17)
  - American Home Products
    - General files, 1986-1987 (Box 17)
  - American Petroleum Institute
    - General files, 1960 Sep.-1961 Oct. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 17)
  - American Red Cross
    - General files, 1957 Feb. (Box 17)
  - Associated Brewing Company
    - General files, 1965 Feb. (Milton Moskowitz files)) (Box 17)
  - Association of Reserve City Bankers
    - General files, 1954 Nov.-1958 June (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 17)
  - AT&T
    - General files, 1970 Jan.-Feb. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 17)
  - Ayerst
    - Credentials presentation, 1986 July 3 (Box 17)
  - Bahamas Tourism
    - General files, 1987-1990 (Box 17)
    - Clippings, 1990 (Box 18)
    - Expression of Interest/Response to Questionnaire for Ministry of Tourism, 1987 (Box 18)
    - JWT capabilities presentation, 1987 (Box 18)
    - J. Walter Travel presentation, 1984 (Box 18)
    - Questionnaire, 1987 (Box 18)
    - Questionnaire response, 1987, 2 folders (Box 18)
    - Statistics, undated (Box 18)
    - Tromson Monroe (subsidiary), 1987 (Box 18)
    - Where Are We And How Do We Get There, presentation, 1980 (Box 18)
  - Ballantine
    - General files, 1963 Oct.-1965 Jan. (Bill Torrey files) (Box 18)
  - Baskin-Robbins
    - Analysis of 1987 Baskin-Robbins Monitor, 1988 (Box 18)
    - Background material, 1989 (Box 18)
    - Backup scripts, 1989, undated (Box 18)
    - Clippings, 1987 (Box 18)
    - Core user study, 1989 (Box 19)
    - Flavor of Success: Baskin-Robbins & the Future, undated (Box 19)
    - Ice cream category in the U.S., 1987, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Nestlé-Findus ice cream overview, 1988 (Box 19)
    - Positioning study, 1989 (Box 19)
    - Promotional calendar proposal, undated (Box 19)
    - Pom plan, 1989 (Box 19)
    - Simmons Choices system reports, 1989 (Box 19)
    - Situation analysis update, 1987 (Box 19)
    - Take home strategy, 1989 (Box 19)
    - Top of mind awareness--places to buy ice cream, diet, yogurt, undated (Box 19)
  - Beatrice Foods
    - Presentation, 1983 (Box 19)
    - Presentation scripts, 1983, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Response to questionnaire, 1983 (Box 19)
  - Beer accounts
    - General files, 1961 June-1962 July (Bill Torrey files) (Box 19)
    - General files, 1963 Oct.-1964 Dec. (Richard Brecker files) (Box 19)
  - Bell Atlantic
    - Credentials presentation, circa 1988 (Box 20)
    - Extending the connection, 1993 (Box 20)
    - JWT organizational charts, 1988 (Box 20)
    - Media resources and research presentation, 1988-1990 (Box 20)
    - Positioning Bell Atlantic for the Future, 1993 (Box 20)
    - Project Unity presentation, 1994 (Box 20)
    - Project Unity--Meeting the Project Unity Creative Requirements, 1993 (Box 20)
    - Staying Ahead of Evolving Marketplace, 1993 (Box 20)
    - Synergy 2000: Consumer Attitudes Towards Bell-Atlantic/TCI Merger, 1993 (Box 20)
  - [Bermuda Department of Tourism, 1999: Removed to Restricted Materials] (Box 20)
  - Blue Chip Stamp Company
    - General files, 1961 Mar.-1961 Sep. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 20)
  - Blue Cross & Blue Shield
    - General files, 1954 Mar.-1964 Apr. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 20)
  - Bosch
    - New product introduction credentials, undated (Box 20)
    - Robert Bosch Corporation and JWT presentation, 1987 (Box 21)
  - Braun
    - About JWT Company, 1973--JWT London (Box 21)
  - Brillo Manufacturing Company
    - General files, 1954 Mar.-1965 Mar. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 21)
  - Burry Biscuit (division of Quaker Oats)
    - General files, 1964 Oct. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 21)
  - Burger King
    - Credentials presentation, circa 1987 (Box 21)
    - Pitch, 1987 (Box 21)
  - California Beef Council
    - General files, 1964 June (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 21)
  - California Raisin Advisory Board
    - General files, 1953 Sep.-1960 July (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 21)
  - California State Lottery
    - Information requested to Respond RFP, 1987 (Box 21)
    - Presentation, 1987, 2 folders (Box 21)
  - California Wine Advisory Board
    - General files, 1956 Oct. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 21)
  - Capitol Cities/ABC
    - Clippings, 1989 (Box 21)
  - Caribbean Tourism Organization
    - Credentials presentation, 1992 (Box 21)
  - Cathay Pacific Airways Ltd. Hong Kong
    - Introducing JWT Company, 1994 (Box 21)
    - Presentation, circa 1994 (Box 21)
  - Champion Spark Plug Company
    - General files, 1950 Nov.-1961 Oct. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 21)
  - Charles Jourdan
    - American licensing file, 1987 (Box 21)
    - American licensing promotional packet, 1987 (Box 21)
    - Cachet Marketing presentation, 1987, 1 of 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Cachet Marketing presentation, 1987 (continued), 2 of 2 folders (Box 22)
  - Chesebrough-Pond's
    - General files, 1955 Mar.-1963 Mar. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 22)
  - Chicago Association of Commerce & Industry
    - General files, 1958 June (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 22)
  - Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul, and Pacific Railroad Company
    - General files, 1957 Mar.-1962 Mar. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 22)
  - Chun King Corporation
    - General files, 1956 Sep.-1965 Feb. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 22)
  - Chunky Chocolate Corporation
    - General files, 1958 Oct.-1961 Apr. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 22)
  - CIBA Vision Care
    - Changing American Consumer presentation, 1985 (Box 22)
  - Cintas
    - Changes at Work: Issues and Opportunities, undated (Box 22)
  - Circuit City
    - General files, 1989, 2 folders (Box 22)
    - Alternate positioning, 1989 (Box 22)
    - Backup scripts, 1989 (Box 22)
    - Brand Central clippings, 1989 (Box 22)
    - Brief, 1989 (Box 22)
    - Clippings, 1989, 2 folders; 1 folder moved to Oversize Materials (Box 22)
    - Company overview, 1988-1989, 2 folders (Box 23)
    - Comprehensive research plan, undated (Box 23)
    - Credentials presentation, 1989, 4 folders (Box 23)
    - Evaluation assignment, 1989 (Box 23)
    - Goldman Sachs research briefs, 1989 (Box 23)
    - Good Guys--Defense of Circuit City's Entry in Northern California, 1989 (Box 23)
    - Good Guys--annual report and case study, 1989 (Box 23)
    - Interviews of salespeople, undated (Box 23)
    - Market study, 1989 Oct. 18 (Box 23)
    - Metro traffic control sponsorship, 1989 (Box 23)
    - Promotional overview, 1989 (Box 23)
    - Sears & Brand Central Introduction, 1989 (Box 23)
  - Clairol
    - 2001--A Woman's Odyssey--JWT Perspective on the Emerging Woman of 21st Century, 1993, 1 of 2 folders (Box 23)
    - 2001--A Woman's Odyssey--JWT Perspective on the Emerging Woman of 21st Century, 1993 (continued), 2 of 2 folders (Box 24)
  - Club Med
    - Company overview, 1987 (Box 24)
    - Credentials presentation, 1984 (Box 24)
    - Interviews, undated (Box 24)
    - Tear sheets, 1983-1984 (Box 24)
  - Coleco
    - Credentials presentation, undated (Box 24)
  - Computer Associates
    - General files, 1988 (Box 24)
    - Agency questionnaire, 1988 (Box 24)
    - Annual report, 1987 (Box 24)
    - Clippings, 1988 (Box 24)
    - Company overview, 1986 (Box 24)
    - Customer education catalog, 1988 (Box 24)
    - Financial reports, 1988 (Box 24)
    - Next Phase presentation, 1988 (Box 24)
    - Where Are We presentation, undated (Box 24)
  - Computerland
    - Credentials presentation, 1983 (Box 24)
    - Questionnaire response, 1983 (Box 24)
  - Congoleum-Nairn
    - General files, 1953 Nov.-1962 Feb. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 24)
  - Continental Airlines
    - General files, 1990, undated (Box 24)
    - 1st Pitch, Credentials presentation, 1986 Aug. 29, 1 of 2 folders (Box 24)
    - 1st Pitch, Credentials presentation, 1986 Aug. 29 (continued), 2 of 2 folders (Box 25)
    - 2nd Pitch, Credentials presentation, 1986 Sep. 10, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Business Month executive travel study, 1987 (Box 25)
    - Memo, 1959 Aug. (Milton Moskowitz files) (Box 25)
    - Proof sketches, undated (Box 25)
    - Turnaround presentation, 1990 (Box 25)
  - Council for Responsible Nutrition (CRN)
    - Credentials presentation, 1988 (Box 25)
    - Response, 1988 (Box 25)